We're back with Jim Parsons.
我们回来了和吉姆·帕森斯一起
And that was a clip from Jim's new show, Call Me Kat, which he's producing.
那是吉姆正在出演的新剧《叫我凯特》的一个片段
And joining us is the star of the show, Mayim Bialik.
加入我们的是这个节目的明星，马伊姆·拜力克
Hi, Mayim.
嗨，马伊姆
How are you?
你好吗？
Hello, Hi.
你好，你好
It's good to see you, and it's great y'all are working
很高兴见到你，很高兴你们在生活大爆炸
together again after Big Bang.
之后又一起工作了
How did this come about?
这是怎么发生的？
Well…
嗯...
Jim came to me...oh, go ahead.
吉姆来找我...哦，你继续
No, no.
不，不
You can say it.
你先说
I came to you while on set one day.
有一天我来找你
Well, Jim came to me, and he said,
吉姆来找我，他说
I want to know what you think about this project that my company has.
我想知道你对我们公司这个项目的看法
It's this Miranda show.
这是米兰达的剧
It was really popular on the BBC.
它在BBC上真的很受欢迎。
And so I went home.
所以我回家之后
I did a little research, and I came back the next day.
我做了点调查，第二天回来之后
And I said, well, Jim, that seems
我说，吉姆，看来
like a really awesome project.
这是一个非常棒的项目
Good luck.
祝你好运
You got my vote of confidence.
你得到了我的信任
And he said, no, I'm asking because I want you to be in it.
他说，不，我问你是因为我想让你参与进来
And I was shocked because I think I'm very annoying.
我很震惊因为我觉得我很烦人
But however annoying I am, he obviously
但不管我多么烦人，他显然
still wanted to work with me.
还想和我一起工作
Yes, Jim?
是的，吉姆？
I think that the annoying quality you bring
我以为你烦人的性格
is what America responds to, Mayim.
是美国人特有的回应，马伊姆
I think that's what this character wanted.
我想这就是这个角色需要的
Right.
对
That's very relatable.
这是与其息息相关的
Everyone love, we know someone annoying, so that's perfect.
每个人都被喜爱，我们需要认识一个让人讨厌的人，所以这是完美的
Tell everybody what the show is about.
告诉大家这个剧是关于什么的
Jim, you want me to take this one, or you want it?
吉姆，你是想让我回答来这个，还是你来？
Well, you're working on it, so please.
噢，你正在出演这个剧，当然是你来回答
OK.
好的
This is a show about a 39-year-old single woman who
这是一部关于一个39岁的单身女人的剧
does not have the life that society often says
她没有过着社会常说的那种
39-year-old women should have.
39岁的单身妇女应该有的标志性的生活
But she's happy anyway.
但她还是很开心
She has an exciting career.
她有一份令人兴奋的事业
She just opened a cat café
她刚开了一家猫咖啡馆
yes, a cat café.
是的，猫咖啡馆
And we have some amazing, amazing guest stars.
我们有一些了不起的来宾
We have Swoosie Kurtz playing my mom, and Leslie Jordan,
我们有史洛希·库尔特扮演我的母亲，还有莱斯利·乔丹
and Cheyenne Jackson, Kyla Pratt, and Julian Gant.
还有夏安·杰克逊，凯拉·普拉特和朱利安·甘特
And we're just having a blast making this show about a very,
我们开心的完成了这个剧关于一个非常
very quirky woman.
非常古怪的女人
She's sloppy. She's messy.
她草率，她混乱
She's sometimes vulgar.
她有时粗俗
She's socially anxious.
她也有社交焦虑
I don't wear Spanx in real life, so she doesn't
我在现实生活中不穿塑身衣，所以她也
have to wear Spanx either.
也不非得穿塑身衣
And that's a really good thing.
这是一件好事
And you work with a lot of cats.
你和很多只猫一起工作
You already, you have three cats, right?
你已经有三只猫了，对吧？
I do.
的确
I am a cat person, and my character is as well.
我是一个猫人，我的角色也是如此
We like to say, she's not a sad cat lady.
我们常常说，她不是一个悲伤的猫咪夫人
She's a rad cat lady.
她是个疯狂的猫夫人。
But you have... I mean, I just,
但你有，我的意思是，我只是，
I look at that, and I think, you know cats, I know cats.
我看了看，我想，你了解猫，我也了解
They usually don't get along.
它们通常一个人呆着
So how do these actor cats all of a sudden meet each other
那么这些猫演员是如何相遇
and not get into these cat fights?
并且不会发生打架之类的事的？
OK, so here's the thing about our cats.
好吧，这是关于我们猫的事情
And I should say, I'm a vegan.
我得说，我是素食主义者
And so I was very, very pleased we
所以我非常非常高兴我们的猫
do not have cats that are tethered or drugged.
没有被绑住或下药
These are just real cats.
这些是真正的猫
Many of them are the Ragdoll breed,
其中许多是布偶猫这个品种
which is a breed that literally likes to chill out.
这是一个喜欢放松的品种
And these cats are raised as kittens
这些猫是从小猫一起长大的
to be around other people and other cats.
和其他人和其他猫一起
The exception is a cat named Piper,
例外的是一只叫派珀的猫
who played Firework, who did not like to be around other cats.
它总是容易与其他的猫有火花，并且不喜欢和其他猫在一起
So we had to kind of block for Piper special.
所以我们不得不为派珀设置一些障碍
So Piper didn't make it?
所以派珀没做到吗？
Piper's audition didn't work out?
派珀的试镜没成功？
Well, Piper just had to be in scenes just with me,
好吧，派珀只是需要和我在一起
and Piper didn't really care for me either.
派珀也不是很在乎我
But Piper looked like a firework.
但派珀像是烟花
We worked around that diva.
我们在那个女主角身边工作过
It's amazing what we'll do in Hollywood.
这是在好莱坞我们做的最神奇的事
We'll put up with anything if you got the right look.
如果你的三观正，我们会忍受一切的
Yeah.
是的
Even with cats, you're right.
即使是对猫来说，你也是对的
That's taking it too far.
这太过分了
And you have not been to the set, Jim,
而且你还没去过现场，吉姆
because of your COVID.
因为你那儿的新冠疫情
But also, you're allergic to cats.
并且你对猫过敏
So how…
所以怎么...
I am.
是的
Yeah, how did you decide to produce a show
是啊，你是怎么决定出演这个剧的
about a bunch of cats knowing you're going
当你知道那儿会有一群猫
to have to visit that set?
并且你不得不去那个片场的时候？
It's the only way he could plan to work with me, if he never
这是他唯一能和我一起工作的方法，如果他从来没有
had to be around me.
必须在我身边
Because I'm so annoying.
因为我太烦人了
No, no. I'll tell you honestly.
不，不。 我老实告诉你
I kind of didn't think of...well, first of all,
我没想到…首先
while we were proposing it, Darlene Hunt,
当我们提议的时候，达琳·亨特
who is running the show, she placed it in the cat cafe.
在主持这个节目，她把它的地点设置在猫咖啡馆里
The original Miranda wasn't.
原来的米兰达不是这样的
And so I didn't realize this nightmare was going
所以我没有意识到我的噩梦
to take place in that way.
将会以这种方式发生
However, there was one time very early on in Big Bang
然而，在生活大爆炸里很早就有一次
where, at one point, they were tossing
在某一时刻，他们在提出
around that idea for a script.
关于着剧本的想法
And they came up and asked me, are you allergic to cats,
他们上来问我，你对猫过敏吗
by any chance?
在任何情况下？
And I said, yeah, I am.
我说，是的，是的
My eyes get puffy and whatever.
我的眼睛会浮肿等等
About a week later, the script showed up
大约一周后，剧本出现了
with a box of Claritin.
和一盒氯雷他定（治疗过敏症状用）一起
And it was like, we're here.
就像，我们在这里
We're going to do one where you're surrounded
我们要在你被包围的环境里做一个
by cats the whole episode.
由猫组成的整个情节
And Mayim was actually there for that.
而马伊姆实际上就在那里
So I have gone through that.
所以我经历了那件事之后发现
And if I don't touch my face, like I keep
如果我不碰我的脸，就像我一直这样
doing right now... there I am.
现在做...我在那儿
Look at that.
你看
But I didn't. I was fine.
但我没有过敏，我很好
I just didn't touch my face. So…
我只是没碰我的脸。 所以…
Wow.
哇哦
I can't believe that they knew you were allergic to cats
我不敢相信他们知道你对猫过敏
and wrote an episode with you surrounded by cats.
还让你一起拍摄被猫包围的剧情
I just…
我只是...
Well, I'll tell you this.
好吧，我告诉你
They asked me a few seasons later
他们几季之后问我
if I could ride a unicycle, and I nearly had a digestive issue.
如果我能骑独轮车，我几乎无法消化这个问题
And I said, no.
我说，不
Because I thought, oh, my God.
因为我想，哦，天哪
They're going to make me do it.
他们会让我这么做的
I'm going to crack my skull open.
我简直快要精神失常
That's just how they roll around here.
他们就是在打这样的主意
Oh, you can't?
哦，你不能？
Well, good luck.
好吧，祝你好运
That's one of Portia's goals is to learn
波西亚的目标之一就是学习
how to ride a unicycle.
如何骑独轮车
She's really interested in unicycles.
她对独轮车很感兴趣
She's never…
她从不...
I imagine it takes a lot of core strength.
我想这需要很多核心力量
Yeah, it takes a lot of core strength.
是的，这需要很大的核心力量
She got a three-cycle instead of a unicycle.
她得到了一辆三轮车，而不是独轮车
And she rides a three-cycle around.
她骑着三轮车转圈
Have you seen those?
你看过那些吗？
Anyway.
不管怎样
I only know it as a tricycle from when I was a little boy.
我小时候就只知道它是三轮车
I don't think I know what this is.
我不知道这是什么
It's like that, but you just sit upright.
就像那样，但你只能坐直了
And there's three things, and you have to still balance it.
而且有三个东西，你仍然需要保持平衡
But it's… anyway.
但是…无论如何
Sorry.
不好意思
I'm just... when I hear you.
我只是…当我听到你的声音时
We should cut to a clip, this is insane.
我们应该把这段剪掉，这太疯狂了
Well, it's called Call Me Kat.
好吧，这部剧叫做《叫我凯特》
It airs Thursdays at 9:00 on Fox.
星期四上午9点在福克斯播出
And great talking to you two.
很高兴和你们聊天
Stay safe, all right?
注意安全，好吗？
You too.
你也是
All right, we'll be right back.
好的，我们马上回来